<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="hello">Hello World, GMapsActivityActivity!</string>
    <string name="app_name">GMapsActivity</string>
    <string name="latitude">Enter the latitude</string>
    <string name="longitude">Enter the Longitude</string>
    <string name="list">Get List</string>
    <string name="Arizona">Arizona</string>
    <string name="WesternRegion">Western Region</string>
    <string name="EasternRegion">Eastern Region</string>
    <string name="aztrails">AZ State Trails</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_all_trail_details">AllTrailDetails</string>
    <string name="title_activity_number_picker_page">NumberPickerPage</string>
    <string name="title_activity_numberpicker_page">NumberpickerPage</string>
    <string name="safetytrail1">Notify someone of your planned hiking route, and when you plan to return.\n\nPark your vehicle on paved surfaces only. Parking on unpaved surfaces erodes preserve land,creates dust and poses a brush-fire risk from hot engine parts.\n\nBe sure that valuables in your vehicle are secured and out of sight.\n\nLock your car and take your car keys with you. Do not hide your keys under a tire or car bumper.\n\nObtain paper trail guides at the trailhead when available, and start your hike with your smartphone fully charged if you plan to reference trails from this app.\n\nReport suspicious activity to park authorities or police.</string>
    <string name="safetytrail2">Check Trail Conditions including temperature, sunset and difficulty.\n\nDownload the trail map to My Trails and reference it often when you hike.\n\nBe prepared for rocky terrain, wild animals and other potential desert hazards.\n\nAlways hike in a group of at least two people.\n\nKnow your own limitations. Don’t try to do more than you are able to.\n\nBe aware of the heat and consider whether to hike at all on the hottest summer days. Even if you are hydrated, you can still suffer from heat-related illnesses.</string>
    <string name="safetytrail3">Bring plenty of water. Each person should have a minimum of one gallon (or about 4 liters) of water per day. Never drink unpurified water from sources along the trails.\n\nWhen hiking in heat, drink 16 to 32 ounces (one-half to one liter) of water per hour in the sun. Drink small amounts often.\n\nIf you are hiking for 4 hours or longer, you should bring sports drinks with electrolytes and salty snacks. \n\nWear appropriate footwear, like hiking boots. Wear light-colored, comfortable clothing. Wear a hat and apply sunscreen.\n\nBring along basic first-aid supplies.</string>
    <string name="safetytrail4">Do not panic if you are injured or lost. Do not wander, stay in one place.\n\nCall the emergency number found in the Trail Details page of the trail you are hiking or call 911.\n\nKnow your location. Look for the nearest trail marker or a noticeable landmark.\n\nIdentify the emergency situation. Be specific about the condition of any injured persons. Call for help from other hikers that may be in the area.</string>
    <string name="safetytrail5">Plan your hike so that you return to your vehicle before sunset. This app estimates hiking time for a roundtrip journey. \n\nStay on the trail. Leaving the trail can cause erosion, interfere with natural habitats and exposes you to unmaintained areas.\n\nStay away from animals and their habitats. Large animals such as bears and mountain lions may be nearby. The desert is home to many snakes and scorpions. Most snake bites occur when people try to handle snakes. Do not attempt to capture or harass snakes or other wildlife. Any animal bite or sting should be examined by a physician and monitored for infection.\n\nWatch for signs of extreme and/or sudden weather changes. Do not cross flooded washes, rivers, deep crevices or ravines. \n\nDo not enter caves without proper equipment. Do not enter mine shafts. \n\nDo not leave your garbage behind. Leave no trace.</string>
    <string name="difficulty1">AZ State Trails difficulty rating is based on the time it should take to hike each trail.\n\nThe difficulty is based on the total distance of the hike, measured in miles, divided by the total time it takes to hike that distance, measured in hours. Elevation is also factored into the difficulty rating.</string>
    <string name="difficulty2">Hikers should always check the weather conditions, elevation change and terrain conditions before hiking. Please reference the Trail Safety page for details on safety precautions.</string>
    <string name="difficulty3">The app provides an estimate for time to complete one roundtrip hike (“there and back”). \n\nThe estimate is based on average hiking speed, change in elevation and average elevation above sea level. Please be mindful of personal ability and seasonal conditions. Your own results may vary.</string>
<string  name="about1">The AZ State Trails app is the official smartphone guide for discovering and hiking trails throughout Arizona.\n\nDiscover trails, check weather conditions, download maps, get safety tips and share postcards with friends and family.\n\nAZ State Trails includes trails from the cities of Phoenix, Scottsdale and Fountain Hills, as well as trails from Maricopa County and Arizona State Parks.\n\nThe app was developed by students in the New Media Innovation Lab at the Walter Cronkite School of Journalism and Mass Communication at Arizona State University.</string>
<string name="about2">Trail data is provided by City of Phoenix Parks and Recreation Department, City of Scottsdale Parks and Recreation, Town of Fountain Hills Parks and Recreation Commission, Maricopa County Parks and Recreation, and Arizona State Parks.\n\nMap data is sourced from Bing Maps, Google Maps and Apple Maps.\n\nWeather data is sourced from the National Weather Service, a department of the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration.\n\nTrail photos are sourced from Panoramio.\n\nApp cover photo by Gene Devine.\n\nLogo and select graphics by Patty Yau.</string>
<string  name="about3">This app does not replace detailed topographic maps and official trail guides. Additionally, it may not always reflect the most current trail path. When in doubt, follow signs on the trail instead of indicators in the app.\n\nThis app includes state trails, and may not list trails in national parks and federal lands, such as trails in Grand Canyon National Park. Additionally, bike paths and some urban pathways are not included.\n\nTrail photos are provided through Panoramio, a free service provided by Google that anyone can contribute photos to. The land management agencies and the ASU New Media Innovation Lab do not endorse, hold copyright for, or ensure the accuracy of the photos provided. The agencies and Arizona State University are not liable for the content provided. Use at your own discretion.\n\nTrail hiking durations are estimates, and will vary based on your ability, trail conditions and other factors. When in doubt, assume a longer hike time than estimated in the app.\n\nGPS locations detected from smartphones are not as accurate as dedicated GPS devices, so results may vary.</string>

</resources>